uniqlo.com 2018-12-28

# Privacy Policy | UNIQLO US

## SITE PRIVACY POLICY

### PRIVACY POLICY

This Privacy Policy applies to the UNIQLO.com website and/or times when you share your personally identifiable information with us through other voluntary means (the “Site”). We value our customers’ privacy and appreciate your confidence that we will respect your privacy in a careful and sensible manner. By visiting the Site and/or using the products and services made available to you on the Site, you are agreeing to the terms of this Privacy Policy. Please read this policy carefully. Our business is constantly evolving and our Privacy Policy and the Site and our [Terms + Conditions](https://www.uniqlo.com/us/en/help/terms-conditions) will also evolve. We may email periodic reminders of our notices and terms of business, unless you have instructed us not to, but you should check our Site frequently to see recent changes. Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Policy applies to all information that we have about you and your account. If you choose to visit the Site, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Policy and our Site’s [Terms + Conditions](https://www.uniqlo.com/us/en/help/terms-conditions).

### WHAT PERSONAL INFORMATION ABOUT CUSTOMERS DOES THE SITE COLLECT?

Here are the types of information we gather:

#### Automatic Information

For each visitor to our Site, our server automatically recognizes information regarding the customer’s domain name (or that of the visitor’s access provider) but not the email address. In this section of the policy, what we define as “information“ means any information you can be contacted by, such as your name (first and last) and your address (city, state, zip). We may also automatically collect other non-personal information such as the type of browser you are using, the address of the website from which your visit originated, the operating system you are using, the domain name of your internet service provider, the pages you visit on the Site and the duration of your visit.

#### Information You Give Us

We also collect and aggregate information volunteered by customers such as when you communicate with us electronically.

#### Cookies

UNIQLO uses cookies and web beacons (also referred to as web bugs, pixel tags or clear GIFs) to manage and secure the Site and email programs. We do not use cookies or web beacons to collect or store personal information. A cookie is a small file placed on your computer when you visit a website. Its purpose is to manage your website experience, help prevent fraud, and allow for customization of the web pages presented to you when you return to the website. Web beacons are small bits of computer code that allow a website owner to track the actions of users on the site and recipients of email communications. Cookies and web beacons help us understand how consumers use the Site and email so we can guard against fraud and design better services in the future. UNIQLO may also use cookies and web beacons to measure the effectiveness of our online advertising initiatives and determine the correlation between UNIQLO customers and the online sites they visit.

### HOW DOES UNIQLO USE THE INFORMATION IT COLLECTS ABOUT CUSTOMERS?

Information about our customers is an important part of our business, and we are not in the business of selling or renting it to any third party. However, if we choose to do so in the future, we will notify you. We share customer information only on a limited basis and with our parent company and affiliates. We share it on a limited basis with agents we use from time to time to send postal mail and email, remove repetitive information from customer lists, analyze data, provide marketing assistance, and provide customer service. We use information about our customers for the specific purpose for which it was volunteered. In addition, if you supply us with your postal address online, you may receive periodic mailings from us with information regarding a new collection, new products, new store locations, or upcoming promotional offers or events. Sometimes we also send offers to selected groups of UNIQLO customers on behalf of other businesses. When we do this, we do not give that business your name and address. If you do not wish to receive such mailings and email updates, or otherwise wish to remove your name from our list, please contact us at [wecare@mail.uniqlo-usa.com](mailto:wecare@mail.uniqlo-usa.com). We release account and other personal information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law; enforce or apply our Site’s [Terms + Conditions](https://www.uniqlo.com/us/en/help/terms-conditions), and/or other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of the Site, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction. However, this does not include selling, renting, sharing, or otherwise disclosing personally identifiable information from customers for commercial purposes in violation of the commitments set forth in this Privacy Policy. In case UNIQLO, or substantially all of its assets are acquired by one or more third parties as a result of a merger, sale, consolidation or liquidation, customer information may be one of the transferred assets.

### CHILDREN’S PRIVACY

UNIQLO is concerned about the privacy protection of children who access the internet, and we comply with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA). Accordingly, the Site is not intended for use by anyone under the age of 13 without the supervision of a parent or guardian, and we do not knowingly collect Information from anyone under 13 years of age without the consent of a parent or guardian. If you are under the age of 13, please do not submit any personal information to us, you may rely on your parent or guardian to assist you.

### CHANGES TO YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

You can make changes by logging in to your UNIQLO account and going to the Profile Page in My Account.

### LINKS TO THIRD PARTY WEBSITES

Certain activities through the Site, such as special promotions, may be linked with those from other unrelated third party companies that offer you the option to share your personal information with the third party. We will not share your personal information with those third party companies; only you can if you make that choice. Links provided on the Site to third party websites are provided as a convenience to you and we do not control those sites or their privacy practices, which may differ from ours. We do not endorse or make any representations about any third party sites that may be accessible through the sites. We encourage you to review the privacy policy of any company before submitting your personal information. The personal data you choose to give to unrelated third parties is covered by their privacy policies, not this Privacy Policy. Some third party companies may choose to share their personal data with us; that sharing is governed by that third party company’s privacy policy.

### OLAPIC PRIVACY POLICY

Note: The privacy policy for Olapic program can be found [here](http://www.olapic.com/privacy-policy/).

### HOW SECURE IS INFORMATION ABOUT YOU?

We are committed to offering our customers a safe and secure environment. Our servers utilize SSL (Secure Sockets Layer) encryption technology to help protect your personal information. By using an SSL-compatible browser such as Netscape Navigator, Microsoft Internet Explorer or AOL, you can help ensure that your personal identifiable information is unavailable to unauthorized users and processed confidentially. In the unlikely event that we believe that the security of your personally identifiable information in our possession or control may have been compromised, we may seek to notify you of that development. If a notification is appropriate or required by law, we would endeavor to do so as promptly as possible under the circumstances, and, to the extent we have your email address, we may notify you by email.

#### By using this Site, you consent to our use of email as a means of such notification

If you have any questions regarding our Privacy Policy, please contact us at [wecare@mail.uniqlo-usa.com](mailto:wecare@mail.uniqlo-usa.com) or by mail at the following address: UNIQLO USA LLC, 450 West 14th Street, 7th Floor, New York, NY 10014, Attn: Marketing and Communications Department

© UNIQLO USA LLC 2006 Last Updated: October 22, 2012

## APP PRIVACY POLICY

### PRIVACY POLICY

This Privacy Policy applies to the UNIQLO Mobile Application and/or times when you share your personally identifiable information with us through other voluntary means (the “App”). We value our customers’ privacy and appreciate your confidence that we will respect your privacy in a careful and sensible manner. By using the App and/or using the products and services made available to you on the App, you are agreeing to the terms of this Privacy Policy. Please read this policy carefully. Our business is constantly evolving and our Privacy Policy and the Site and our [Terms + Conditions](https://www.uniqlo.com/us/en/help/terms-conditions) will also evolve. We may email periodic reminders of our notices and terms of business, unless you have instructed us not to, but you should check our App frequently to see recent changes. Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Policy applies to all information that we have about you and your account. If you choose to use the App, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Policy and our Site’s [Terms + Conditions](https://www.uniqlo.com/us/en/help/terms-conditions).

### WHAT PERSONAL INFORMATION ABOUT CUSTOMERS DOES THE APP COLLECT?

Here are the types of information we gather:

#### Automatic Information

For each visitor to our App, our server automatically recognizes information regarding the customer’s domain name (or that of the visitor’s access provider) but not the email address. In this section of the policy, what we define as “information” means any information you can be contacted by, such as your name (first and last) and your address (city, state, zip). We may also automatically collect other non-personal information such as the type of browser you are using, the address of the website from which your visit originated, the operating system you are using, the domain name of your internet service provider, the pages you visit on the App and the duration of your visit.

#### Information You Give Us

We also collect and aggregate information given to us, such as your purchase history, purchase date, purchase store, and coupon usage (including location and date(s)).

#### Cookies

UNIQLO uses cookies and web beacons (also referred to as web bugs, pixel tags or clear GIFs) to manage the App and email programs. We do not use cookies or web beacons to collect or store personal information. A cookie is a small file placed on your computer when you visit a website. Its purpose is to manage your website experience and allow for customization of the web pages presented to you when you return to the website. Web beacons are small bits of computer code that allow a website owner to track the actions of users on the site and recipients of email communications. Cookies and web beacons help us understand how consumers use the Site and email so we can design better services in the future. UNIQLO may use cookies and web beacons to measure the effectiveness of our online advertising initiatives and determine the correlation between UNIQLO customers and the online sites they visit.

### HOW DOES UNIQLO USE THE INFORMATION IT COLLECTS ABOUT CUSTOMERS?

Information about our customers is an important part of our business, and we are not in the business of selling or renting it to any third party. However, if we choose to do so in the future, we will notify you. We share customer information only on a limited basis and with our parent company and affiliates. We share it on a limited basis with agents we use from time to time to send postal mail and email, remove repetitive information from customer lists, analyze data, provide marketing assistance, and provide customer service. We use information about our customers for the specific purpose for which it was volunteered. In addition, if you supply us with your postal address online, you may receive periodic mailings from us with information regarding a new collection, new products, new store locations, or upcoming promotional offers or events. Sometimes we also send offers to selected groups of UNIQLO customers on behalf of other businesses. When we do this, we do not give that business your name and address. If you do not wish to receive such mailings and email updates, or otherwise wish to remove your name from our list, please contact us at [wecare@mail.uniqlo-usa.com](mailto:wecare@mail.uniqlo-usa.com). We release account and other personal information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law; enforce or apply our Site’s [Terms + Conditions](https://www.uniqlo.com/us/en/help/terms-conditions), and/or other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of the Site, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction. However, this does not include selling, renting, sharing, or otherwise disclosing personally identifiable information from customers for commercial purposes in violation of the commitments set forth in this Privacy Policy. In case UNIQLO, or substantially all of its assets are acquired by one or more third parties as a result of a merger, sale, consolidation or liquidation, customer information may be one of the transferred assets.

### CHILDREN’S PRIVACY

UNIQLO is concerned about the privacy protection of children who access the internet, and we comply with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA). Accordingly, the Site is not intended for use by anyone under the age of 13 without the supervision of a parent or guardian, and we do not knowingly collect Information from anyone under 13 years of age without the consent of a parent or guardian. If you are under the age of 13, please do not submit any personal information to us, you may rely on your parent or guardian to assist you.

### CHANGES TO YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

You can make changes by logging in to your UNIQLO account and going to the Profile Page in My Account.

### LINKS TO THIRD PARTY WEBSITES

Certain activities through the Site, such as special promotions, may be linked with those from other unrelated third party companies that offer you the option to share your personal information with the third party. We will not share your personal information with those third party companies; only you can if you make that choice. Links provided on the Site to third party websites are provided as a convenience to you and we do not control those sites or their privacy practices, which may differ from ours. We do not endorse or make any representations about any third party sites that may be accessible through the sites. We encourage you to review the privacy policy of any company before submitting your personal information. The personal data you choose to give to unrelated third parties is covered by their privacy policies, not this Privacy Policy. Some third party companies may choose to share their personal data with us; that sharing is governed by that third party company’s privacy policy.

### HOW SECURE IS INFORMATION ABOUT YOU?

We are committed to offering our customers a safe and secure environment. Our servers utilize SSL (Secure Sockets Layer) encryption technology to help protect your personal information. By using an SSL-compatible browser such as Netscape Navigator, Microsoft Internet Explorer or AOL, you can help ensure that your personal identifiable information is unavailable to unauthorized users and processed confidentially. In the unlikely event that we believe that the security of your personally identifiable information in our possession or control may have been compromised, we may seek to notify you of that development. If a notification is appropriate or required by law, we would endeavor to do so as promptly as possible under the circumstances, and, to the extent we have your email address, we may notify you by email.

#### By using this Site, you consent to our use of email as a means of such notification

If you have any questions regarding our Privacy Policy, please contact us at [wecare@mail.uniqlo-usa.com](mailto:wecare@mail.uniqlo-usa.com) or by mail at the following address: UNIQLO USA LLC, 450 West 14th Street, 7th Floor, New York, NY 10014, Attn: Marketing and Communications Department

© UNIQLO USA LLC 2017 Last Updated: September 20, 2017
